>> Brian Holt: 接下来我们要做的是服务器端呈现，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So the next section we're
going to do is server side rendering,
这将使我们成为 Node.js ，我喜欢 Node.js。
which is going to get us into Node.js,
which I love Node.js.
我的工作就是在 Azure上做 Node.js
That's literally my job is
to work on Node.js at Azure.
所以我要尝试不覆盖 Node.js ，因为这不是 Node.js
So I'm going to try and not cover a ton
of Node.js, because this is not a Node.js
在 Fronend Masters上，研讨会和 Node.js 内容丰富。
workshop and there's plenty of good
Node.js content on Frontend Masters.
所以我们要尽量把这个尽量少一点
So we're gonna keep this as
bare minimum as possible.
> > Brian Holt: 所以我们需要做一些事情来准备
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So there's a couple
things that we have to do to prepare for
服务器端呈现。
server side rendering.
我想，让我们先谈谈为什么要服务器端呈现。
And, I guess, let's talk first about
why you want to server side render.
如果你现在去我们的应用程序然后按 " 查看来源"
If you go to our app right now and
you hit View Source,
你可以看到这里什么都没有对吧
you can see here there's nothing here,
right?
这里什么都没有
There's absolutely nothing here.
因此，这意味着我们必须下载所有 JavaScript ，然后让它呈现，并且
So that means we have to download all the
JavaScript, and then have it render, and
那就会被加载了对吧
then it'll load, right?
如果能下载就更好了，给用户看点东西，
Wouldn't it be better if it could just
download, and show the user something, and
然后在后台装入 JavaScript ，对吗 ?
then in the background load JavaScript,
right?
这就是服务器端呈现的方式。
So that's what server side
render is going to do.
它允许我们把所有申请都写在 React中
It allows us to write all of
our application in React,
预呈现所有内容，然后向用户发送完整的标记。
pre-render everything, and
then send the user the complete markup.
然后，当完成加载后， React 将接管该页面。
And then React will take over
the page once it's finished loading.
所以我们需要做几件事情来做准备。
So we have to do a couple of
things to prepare for that.
我们要做的第一件事就是我们要做一个新的文件
The first thing that we're going to do is,
we're going to make a new file called
ClientApp.js， >> Brian Holt: And
ClientApp.js,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
这将会是只在浏览器中运行的所有代码，对吗 ?
this is gonna be all the code that
runs only in the browser, right?
想象如果你用谷歌分析之类的东西
So imagine if you're using
things like Google Analytics,
Node.js 的工作对吧
that doesn't work in Node.js, right?
我很抱歉我不知道
I'm sorry, it doesn't.
但你可以在这里做
But you could do that here.
所以我们会说进口反应是反应的
So here we're gonna say
import React from react,
从反应 - dom导入呈示。
import render from react-dom.
导入，对不起，不反应，呈现，但我们实际上是要进口水化物。
Import, I'm sorry, not react, render, but
we're actually going to import hydrate.
从 ./app 导入应用程序。
Import app from ./app.
然后我们就会说水合物应用
And then we're going to say hydrate App
document.getElementById ('root'));
at document.getElementById('root'));
> > Brian Holt: 然后你会说
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here you would say
任何其他的浏览器
any other browser-only things.
换句话说，这部分不会在浏览器中运行。
In other words, this part's not
gonna get run in the browser.
因此，水合物是一种特殊的功能。
So hydrate is a special function.
就像呈现，但是
It's like render, but
我想说这地方已经有标记了
what it's saying is I expect there
to be markup already in this place.
只要接管那里就好了别再渲染了对吧
Just take over what's there,
don't re render, right?
而如果我说的是此处而不是水合物
Whereas, if I said render here
instead of hydrate it would say
把它炸掉然后重新呈现
blow away whatever is there and
re-render it.
就像我不在乎里面有什么对吧
Like I don't care what's in there, right?
>> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
那我们就去 App.js
Then we're gonna go to App.js here.
我将在最后删除这部分
And I'm going to delete
this part at the end, and
我要说出口默认应用
I'm just gonna say export default App.
现在，我可以将它导入节点，然后在节点上呈现。
And then now, I can import this
into Node and then render it there.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，现在你要通过整个应用程序了，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, now you have to
go through your entire application,
并确保初始首次呈现没有文档的引用。
and make sure on the initial first render
that there's no reference to documents.
在这种修复中，有一个，它在模态中。
In this repo there is one,
and it's in modal.
如何声明 document.getElementById?
Notice where it says
document.getElementById?
如果你想在节点上做这个，它就不会感谢你了，对吧 ?
If you try to do this in node,
it's gonna say no thank you, right?
所以我们要做的是我们要说
So what we're gonna do
instead is we're gonna say,
我们要把这一切都转移到这里
we're just gonna move this
into the effect here.
好吗 ?
Okay?
这只会在效果中发生，那就好了。
Now this will only happen in the effect,
and that'll be fine.
>> Brian Holt: 接下来我要你做的事，我们要安装两个新的东西。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Next thing I want you to
do, we're going to install two new things.
我们要说 npm 的安装
We're going to say npm install
是用 CLI 和快递来的
babel-cli and express.
巴贝 CLI 我们得通过巴贝尔来运行我们的雷法密码
Babel CLI, cuz we're gonna have to run
our React code through Babel, right,
因为节点不会说 JSX。
because Node doesn't speak JSX.
然后， Express 只是其中一个节点框架。
And then Express is just one
of the many Node frameworks.
我们只会用它最受欢迎的那种
We're just gonna use that one
cuz it's the most popular one.
>> Brian Holt: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay.
接下来我们要做的事
Next thing that we're gonna do.
我们要走了吗
Is we're gonna go and
内置
make inside of
package.json。
package.json.
我们要做个建筑
We're gonna make a build.
所以在剧本里我们要说的是建筑
So here in scripts, we're gonna say build.
这就是如何构建应用程序以实现生产的方法。
And this is how you build your
application for production.
我们会说要建个包裹
We're gonna say build parcel build
--公用 URL ./dist src/index.html。
--public-url ./dist src/index.html.
> > Brian Holt: 所以这会告诉包裹，嘿，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
this is gonna tell parcels, hey,
构建我的代码以进行生产。
build my code for production.
然后这个公开的公开的部分说我要为你服务
And then this public-url part says that
I'm going to be serving everything from
/ dist，因此请注意此问题。
/dist, so be aware of that.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，然后在这里，我们也要开始。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and then down here,
we're also gonna put in a start.
这将会是 npm 运行的基础
And that's gonna be npm run build
&& babel-node server/index.js.
&amp;&amp; babel-node server/index.js.
现在我要用巴伯的方式
Now, I'm gonna use babel-node.
通常不推荐使用此产品。
This is typically not recommended for
production use.
但这会救我们很多人
But it's going to save
us a lot of setting up.
通常您要执行的是预先编译您的 React 代码，以便
Typically what you would do is you'd pre
compile your React code in such a way that
节点可以读取它，然后使用该代码以使其没有任何 JSX，对吗 ?
Node could read it, and then use that code
so that it doesn't have any JSX, right?
但今天，这需要一段时间。
But today, that would take a while.
这并不是真的有用的练习。
And that's not really that
useful of an exercise.
因此，只要知道有更好的方法可以做到这一点。
So just be aware that there's
a better way to do this.
我们要在这里做捷迳
We're just going to kind
of shortcut it here.